4seating.com 2016-10-16

# Privacy Policy

Have Any Questions?  1-800-407-8665

###### FREE 24-HOUR SHIPPING!

Contiguous U.S.

|

###### NO SALES TAX!

(excl. CA & TX)

**Welcome to 4seating.com,** The place for HOME THEATER SEATING! We have the largest selection of in-stock and ready-to-ship home theater seating and home theater furniture available! We offer theater seating and design solutions for both the casual and professional home theater enthusiast. Call us on our toll free line 1-800-407-8665 with any questions. We also have a complete line of custom home theater decor available.

The **Seatcraft Venetian** home theater seating is fully loaded with great features! This media room chair comes complete with lighted cupholders and base, free tray tables, and hidden in-arm storage. This is one of our best selling home theater seats!

The **Barcalounger Gala** is constructed with a “memory cool gel” that keeps its material cool. Memory foam cushioning snugly contours to your natural body shape. This home theater seat also comes with USB ports on the power recline mechanism.

The stylish **Seatcraft Seville** home theater seats provide a new dimension of comfort. These chairs are constructed with leather gel, which was designed to replicate the smooth texture, swank appearance and supremely soft feel of top grain leather, at an outstanding value.

The [**Seatcraft Rialto**](http://4seating.com/seatcraft-tiered-home-theater-seating-no-risers) home theater seating setup eliminates the need for risers! It comes in a Front Row style, Back Row style, and the Standard style Rialto chair. The front row theater seat is shorter than the standard Rialto. The back row theater seating has been raised so that you do not need a riser to see over the middle row! Now you can get stadium style seating without the risers, or the additional cost!

[**Home theater seating Powered by Soundshaker,**](http://4seating.com/seatcraft-tiered-home-theater-seating-no-risers) a new revolution in home theater entertainment. This exciting piece of hi-ttech wizardry will allow you to feel the screen action, without leaving the comfort of your seat! Immerse yourself in your favorite films like never before: you will not only see and hear, but live each moment as your chair vibrates to each car chase or explosion. A whole new dimension in cinema thrills awaits. Each chair comes equipped with the SoundShaker technology. *Amplifier sold separate

4seating.com has been providing quality Home Theater Seats for over 10 years! We manufacture or own line or theater seating, as well as purchase bulk orders from such companies as Berkline, Palliser, Coaster, and Jaymar. This allows us to maintain or low prices for you, the consumer! These articles are provided for you to elevate your home theater experience to the highest quality!

[The Seatcraft Aston](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/07/the-aston.html)   **|** [  On Home Theater Decor, Part 1](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/06/on-home-theater-decor-part-one.html)   **|** [  On Home Theater Decor, Part 2](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/07/on-home-theater-decor-part-two.html)   **|** [  10 Movies to Show Off Your Home Theater](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/02/the-top-ten-movies-to-show-off-your.html)   **|** [  Montage Extended Warranty](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/01/the-montage-extended-warranty.html)   **|** [  Finding The Right Seat for Your Home Theater](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/01/finding-right-home-theater-seat.html)   **|** [  Leather Care and Maintenance](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/01/leather-care-and-maintenance.html)   **|** [  Product Spotlight: Palliser](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/01/spotlight-palliser.html)   **|** [  Product Spotlight: Klaussner](http://blog.4seating.com/2013/01/spotlight-klaussner.html)   **|**   Find Your Home Theater Deals   **|**   The Seatcraft Accessory POD   **|**   Seatcraft Rialto Stage Seating   **|**   Seatcraft Home Theater Seating Line   **|**   The Largest Theater Seating Showroom in Los Angeles \ Orange County Area   **|**   Home Theater Gear is a Booming Business   **|**   Berkline, Palliser, Seatcraft, Coaster, and Jaymar Theater Seating   **|**   Home Theater Seating Fabrics and Leathers   **|**   DOLBY Surround Home Theater Guide

▪ Privacy Policy

* * *

We are committed to respecting your privacy and protecting the necessary personal information you share with us. This includes your Name, Phone numbers, addresses, email address, etc. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of the ways we will use the information we collect from you. If you do not agree with this policy, you should not use our website.

▪ Collecting Information

* * *

We will need you to provide certain information about yourself (such as name, address, phone number, email address, etc.) when you place an order for products, samples, services, etc. This information may be used to contact you with questions or issues regarding your order. We will also maintain a record of the products and services you have purchased from us. It is completely your choice whether or not to provide us this information. However, you will not be able to purchase products or services from us without this information. In using our websites, you will remain anonymous unless personal information is volunteered to us.

▪ Use of Your Information

* * *

The personal information you provide will be used for internal purposes, such as confirming and tracking your order and notifying you of specials, promotions, services, and offers. We may share information with companies who provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, and data management. We may also disclose your information in instances where the law requires us to do so.

▪ Editing and Updating Personal Information

* * *

If you prefer we do not contact you regarding specials, promotions, services, and offers, please email your request to [support@4seating.com](mailto:support@4seating.com) and include your order number or name and phone number. Please do the same if you would like to update your information if you have moved or changed phone numbers or email addresses and would still like to receive communications from us.

▪ Security

* * *

We take all necessary precautions when it comes to protecting your information. We use a secure server with sophisticated encryption and authentication tools. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed 100% secure. It is a main priority of ours to protect your privacy and information. However, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to and from our web sites. This is done at your own risk.
